<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>                                                                                                 
<!--                                                                                                
uiIndex           number of hint, 0 is a template that will not be selected
szName            text to appear, 256 chars max

A hint can appear according to its flags. So a int that only has the <food>-tag will only appear if playing with the food system. 

The other tags determine in what category this hint falls, and will be displayed accordingly
-->                                                                                                 
<LOADSCREENHINTS>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>0</uiIndex>
    <szName>This template should never show up</szName>
    <lore>0</lore>
    <weapons>0</weapons>
    <items>0</items>
    <keybind>0</keybind>
    <food>0</food>
    <zombie>0</zombie>
    <overheat>0</overheat>
    <ncth>0</ncth>
    <covertops>0</covertops>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>1</uiIndex>
    <szName>Most machineguns have replacable barrels. Use this to rapidly cool down your gun during combat.</szName>
    <overheat>1</overheat>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>2</uiIndex>
    <szName>Use your knife on a corpse to retrieve its uniform, or pick up the corpse.</szName>
    <covertops>1</covertops>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>3</uiIndex>
    <szName>Spies can use enemy uniforms to disguise as soldiers.</szName>
    <covertops>1</covertops>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>4</uiIndex>
    <szName>You can toggle between different scopes and sights by pressing'.'.</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>5</uiIndex>
    <szName>Leaving food around for a few days will spoil it, making it unhealthy.</szName>
    <food>1</food>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>6</uiIndex>
    <szName>You can clean poisoning by taking an antidote, or the DOCTOR assignment.</szName>
    <food>1</food>
    <zombie>1</zombie>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>7</uiIndex>
    <szName>If a 'M' appears on your gun, that means it is currently mounted onto something, resulting in better stability.</szName>
    <weapons>1</weapons>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>8</uiIndex>
    <szName>Don't forget to check out Jagged Alliance: Flashback on Kickstarter!</szName>
    <lore>1</lore>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>9</uiIndex>
    <szName>Don't be lame! Drop backpacks with [SHIFT]+[B] in tactical to enhance movement and enable climbing.</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>10</uiIndex>
    <szName>Need help? Help yourself by pressing [H] in strategic screen. And visit the helping bears at www.ja-galaxy-forum.com</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
    <lore>1</lore>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>11</uiIndex>
    <szName>Turn the wheel to your fortune. Increase Chance To Hit in all fire modes with the mouse [WHEEL]. [ALT]+[WHEEL] sets size of auto-fire volley.</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>12</uiIndex>
    <szName>Facilities granted. Some sectors offer facilities like bars or mines that you can assign mercs to in strategical. Tool tips hinting at facility's function appear when assigning a merc just like you'd assign a merc to repairing, doctoring or training militia.</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
    <lore>1</lore>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>13</uiIndex>
    <szName>Guild of Thieves. Steal opponent's gun with the hand-cursor [CTRL]+[LEFTCLICK]. If enemy is kissing the dust in a non-dying state you may strip off really everything carried including additional ammo and armour.</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
    <lore>1</lore>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>14</uiIndex>
    <szName>EOD flag signals. Mind you, the blue flag you may put in a tile on ground to mark a mine or trap you've spotted is also seen and reacted to by the enemy.</szName>
    <lore>1</lore>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>15</uiIndex>
    <szName>Colour your vision! Holding [END] in tactical shows currently selected merc's detailed field of vision, ranging from red (don't spot nobody) to green (spot even somebody lying in the grass).</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>16</uiIndex>
    <szName>Red Alert! Holding [DEL] in tactical shows where enemies you know of may see currently selected merc, ranging from red (will be seen even prone) to green (perfect concealment).</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>17</uiIndex>
    <szName>Jagged windowing. Shoot the glass (where necessary), face the open window and climb through it with [SHIFT]+[J].</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>18</uiIndex>
    <szName>While in sector inventory, click empty inventory slots for a list of items you may want to put there.</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>19</uiIndex>
    <szName>While in sector inventory, click empty attachment slots for a list of compatible attachments.</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>20</uiIndex>
    <szName>While in sector inventory, [CTRL] click empty inventory slots for a categorized list of items in that sector.</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>21</uiIndex>
    <szName>When choosing items via popup menus (accessible through clicking empty inventory/attachment slots), least damaged items are used.</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>22</uiIndex>
    <szName>Press [CTRL]+[SHIFT]+[X] to enable real-time sneaking. When active, you won't enter turn-based mode when you spot enemy soldiers - as long as they are not alerted of your presence.</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
  <LOADSCREENHINT>
    <uiIndex>23</uiIndex>
    <szName>Press [CTRL]+[X] to enter turn-based mode while real-time sneaking is active. Only works when you see enemy soldiers.</szName>
    <keybind>1</keybind>
  </LOADSCREENHINT>
</LOADSCREENHINTS>